Register of the Christopher Temple Emmet Papers 1913-1974
Hoover Institution Archives
- SUBJECT FILE, 1938-1974
  - Non-Partisan Committee to Defeat Hamilton Fish
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization
    - General
    - Parliamentarians' Conference, 5th, Washington, November 15-21, 1959
  - Nuclear Non-Proliferation Treaty, 1968
    - General
    - Adherence of West Germany
  - Nuclear Test Ban Treaty, 1963
  - Olympic games, 1956
  - Oppenheimer, Ernest J.
  - Oriel, Benjamin (Box 47)
  - Overseas Press Club of America
    - General
    - Freedom of the Press Committee
  - Palestine - History - 1917-1948
  - Peter, Bishop Janos
  - Peter II, King
  - Petkov, Nikola
  - Petroleum industry and trade
    - General
    - Embargo, 1973-1975
  - Pilgrims (organization)
  - Plain Talk
  - Poland - History - 1945- (Box 48)
  - Polish American Congress
  - Polish Medical Aid Project
  - Polish Telegraph Agency
  - Poznan, Poland - Riots, 1956
  - Presidents - U.S. - Election
    - 1960
    - 1964
    - 1972
  - Press
  - Price regulation - Canada
  - Procope, Hjalmar J.
  - Public opinion - Germany, West
  - Race discrimination
  - Radio Free Europe
  - Radio stations - U.S.
  - Rally in Defense of Poland and Europe, New York, May 20, 1945
  - Rapacki Plan
  - Reconstruction (1939-1951)
    - Belgium
    - Germany
    - Great Britain
  - Refugees, Chinese - Hong Kong (Box 49)
  - Refugees, Cuban
  - Refugees, German
  - Refugees, Hungarian
    - General
    - Austria
  - Refugees, Jewish
  - Refugees, Political
  - Refugees, Vietnamese
  - Refugees Defense Committee
  - Religion in Communist Dominated Areas
  - Remember Berlin Day
  - Republican Party (U.S.)
    - National conventions
      - 1956
      - Chicago, 1960
      - San Francisco, 1964 (Box 50)
    - Platform, 1956 - "Captive nations" plank
  - Restitution and indemnification claims (1933- )
    - Austria
    - Germany, West
  - Revolutionary Council of Hungary
  - Richardson, John, Jr.
  - Rosenberg, Julius and Ethel
  - Rostow, Eugene V.
  - Russia
    - Economic conditions
    - Foreign relations
      - General
      - China
      - Germany
  - Russo-German Treaty, 1939
  - Sager, Peter
  - Scholl, Inge
  - Search for New Directions Weekend Institute, Hudson Guild Farm, Andover, New Jersey, March 6-8, 1959
  - Shashahani, Reza
  - Shirer, William L., The Rise and Fall of the Third Reich
  - Sinai Campaign, 1956 (Box 51)
  - Society for the Prevention of World War III
  - Socor, Vladimir M.
  - South Moluccas, Republic of the
  - Spaak, Paul Henri
  - Spain - History
    - Civil War, 1936-1939 - Refugees
    - 1939-present
  - Staden, Ambassador Berndt von
  - Stalin, Joseph - Attitude toward fascism
  - Stein, Guenther
  - Student Coordinating Committee for Peace and Freedom in Vietnam
  - Student Friends of the Captive Nations
  - Students for Democratic Action
  - Subramanyan, A.
  - Susan Garth Biafran Babies' Appeal
  - Testimonial to the Martyrs of Communist Tyranny, New York, June 14, 1959
  - Tito, President Josip Broz
  - Trade-unions and communism - U.S.
  - Tshombe Emergency Committee
  - Turkey - Foreign relations
  - U-2 incident, 1960
  - Ukrainian Bulletin - Attack on American Friends of the Captive Nations (Box 52)
  - United Nations
    - General
    - Conference on International Organization, San Francisco, 1945
    - Monetary and Financial Conference, Bretton Woods, 1944
    - Relief and Rehabilitation Administration
  - U.S.
    - Committee for the United Nations
    - Congress
      - House
        - Committee on Un-American Activities
        - Special Committee on Un-American Activities (1938-1944)
      - Senate. Subcommittee on Internal Security
    - Economic conditions
    - Emigration and immigration
    - Foreign economic relations
      - General
      - Europe, Eastern
        - Clippings
        - Memoranda
        - Printed matter, miscellaneous
      - Germany, West (Box 53)
      - Russia
        - General
          - Memoranda
          - Printed matter
        - Wheat sale, 1963
    - Foreign relations
      - General
      - China
      - Cuba
      - Europe, Eastern
      - Europe, Western
      - Germany (Box 54)
      - Germany, West
      - Great Britain
      - Hungary
      - Japan
      - Russia
      - Taiwan
      - Vietnam
    - Freedom Academy, Proposals for
      - 1956-1957
      - 1960-1963
      - 1964
      - 1965-1967
    - Full employment policies
    - Information Agency
    - Military policy
      - General
      - Antiballistic missile system
        - Memoranda
        - Printed matter (Box 55)
      - Europe
        - Clippings
        - Notes
        - Printed matter, miscellaneous
      - Germany, West
    - Office of War Information
    - Politics and government
      - 1945-1953
      - 1961-1963
      - 1963-1969
      - 1969-1974
    - Relations (general) with Germany
    - Relations (general) with Russia
    - Social conditions
  - U.S. Stake in the U.N. Conference, 5th American Assembly, Columbia University, Harriman, New York, July 30-August 2, 1954
  - Universities and colleges - Germany, West
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars of the U.S.
  - Viereck, George Sylvester
  - Vietnam - History - 1954-1961
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War
  - Vietnam Veterans for a Just Peace
  - Vietnamese Conflict, 1961-1975 (Box 56)
    - General
      - Clippings
      - Correspondence
      - Drafts of writings
      - Memoranda and notes
      - Printed matter, miscellaneous
    - Cambodia incursion, May 1970
    - Laos
  - Volunteer Christian Committee to Boycott Nazi Germany
    - Boycott pledges
    - Clippings (Box 57)
    - Correspondence
    - Financial records
    - Memoranda
    - Printed matter, miscellaneous
    - Stamp plates
  - Wallace, Vice President Henry A.
  - War crime trials
    - Bulgaria
    - Germany, West
    - Helsinki, 1946 (Box 58)
    - Nuremberg
  - Watergate incident
  - Wehrkunde (Defense Studies) Conference, Munich, February 1-2, 1969
  - White, Harry Dexter
  - White, William Allen - Resignation from Committee to Defend America by Aiding the Allies
  - Willkie, Wendell L.
  - Women for Freedom
  - Woodrow Wilson Foundation
  - Workers Defense League
  - World Anti-Communist Congress for Freedom and Liberation
  - World Bill of Rights Association, Mass meeting, New York, March 3, 1946
  - World Congress of Intellectuals in Defense of Peace, Wroclaw, Poland, August 1948
  - World Fellowship, Inc.
  - World War, 1939-1945
    - Atrocities
    - China
    - Civilian relief
      - China
      - Poland
    - Czechoslovak Republic
    - Forced repatriation
    - Germany
    - Great Britain
    - Greece
    - India
    - Peace
    - Poland (Box 59)
      - Clippings
      - Correspondence
      - Memoranda
      - Pamphlets
      - Printed matter, miscellaneous
    - Propaganda
    - Reparations
      - General
        - Clippings
        - Correspondence
        - Memoranda
        - Printed matter, miscellaneous
      - Morgenthau Plan
    - Russia
  - Young Men's Christian Association (Box 60)
  - Zellerbach Commission on the European Refugee Situation
  - Zionism - Palestine
    - Clippings
    - Memoranda
    - Press releases
    - Printed matter, miscellaneous
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1935-1974
  Correspondence arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
  - Unidentified, 1943-1973 (Box 60)
  - ABC-TV, 1963
  - Abegg, Lily, 1949
  - Aber, L. Louis, 1939
  - Abernethy, John T., 1964
  - Aboud, Ambassador El Mehdi ben, 1959
  - Acheson, Alice (Mrs. Dean), 1971
  - Acheson, Dean, 1946-1971
  - Achminow, Herman F., 1967
  - Ackerman, Robert V., 1946
  - Adair, Representative E. Ross, 1959
  - Adams, Sherman, 1958
  - Addabbo, Representative Joseph P., 1969
  - Adler, Warren, 1957
  - Agar, Herbert, 1946-1953
  - Agar, William, 1944-1946
  - Agnew, Clark, 1947 (Box 61)
  - Agnich, Richard J., 1969
  - Aiken, Mr., 1936
  - Aiken, Senator George, 1971
  - Albats, Bruno, 1970
  - Albers, Rose R., 1952
  - Aldrich, Amey, 1946
  - Aldrich, Margaret Chanler, 1959
  - Aldrich, Ambassador Winthrop, 1953
  - Alexander, Archibald S., 1959-1960
  - Alexander, W. B., 1947
  - Alfange, Dean, 1944-1945
  - Algase, Gertrude, 1945
  - Alland, Alexander, Jr., 1965
  - Allemann, F. R., 1973
  - Allen, Douglas H., 1960
  - Allen, Frederick Lewis, 1947
  - Allen, George V., 1949-1958
  - Allen, Raymond B., 1952
  - Allen, Richard V., 1969
  - Allen, Will, 1946-1947
  - Allison, Robert, 1946
  - Allott, Senator Gordon, 1959-1963
  - Almond, Governor J. Lindsay, Jr., 1961
  - Alsop, Joseph, 1951-1966
  - Alsop, Stewart, 1950-1972
  - Altschul, Frank, 1957-1973
  - Ambroz, Oton, 1969
  - American Association for the United Nations, 1946
  - American Labor Conference on International Affairs, 1945
  - American Veterans of World War II, 1958
  - Amerikai Magyar Nepszava, 1950
  - Anders, Joseph, 1959
  - Anders, General Wladyslaw, 1956
  - Anderson, Mr., 1956
  - Anderson, Charles D., 1940
  - Anderson, Senator Clinton P., 1960
  - Anderson, Douglas, 1958
  - Anderson, Representative Glenn M., 1969
  - Anderson, Harry B., 1973
  - Anderson, Mary R., 1939
  - Andrews, Paul Shipman, 1947
  - Andrews, Rebecca, 1955
  - Anfuso, Representative Victor L., 1956-1962
  - Angell, Ernest, 1944-1946
  - Angell, Sir Norman, 1945
  - Angoff, Charles, 1946
  - Antonini, Luigi, 1945
  - App, Austin J., 1947
  - Appleby, Robert R., 1941
  - Araujo, Ambassadr Alfonso, 1958
  - Arensberg, Mariada C., 1963
  - Argast, Charles E., 1962
  - Argov, Shlomo, 1970
  - Armstrong, Anne, 1964-1973
  - Armstrong, Christa (Mrs. Hamilton Fish), 1955-1960
  - Armstrong, Hamilton Fish, 1949-1971
  - Armstrong, Margaret, 1945-1947
  - Armstrong, Representative O. K., 1955
  - Aronson, Frances, 1957
  - Arthur, Robert, 1959
  - Arvin, Newton, 1949
  - Ascoli, Max, 1949-1968
  - Ashford-Russell, B. H., 1961
  - Atkinson, Brooks, 1949
  - Atterbury, Marguerite, 1955
  - Attlee, Prime Minister Clement R., 1946-1955
  - Au, David W. K., 1952
  - Aubert, Theodore, 1947
  - Auchincloss, Douglas, 1949
  - Auer, Paul de, 1959-1962
  - Austin, Warren R., 1950
  - Azkoul, Ambassador Karim, 1958
  - Baade, Fritz, 1949 (Box 62)
  - Babb, M. W., 1959
  - Bachkai, Bela, 1963
  - Backer, George, 1949-1973
  - Backer, John H., 1972-1973
  - Bacon, Charles L., 1961
  - Bacon, Virginia, 1949-1957
  - Badeau, John S., 1956
  - Baecker, Werner, 1963
  - Baehr, Harry, 1956-1960
  - Bahr, Eugen, 1963
  - Bailey, Wes, 1944-1945
  - Bailley, Maria, 1952-1973
  - Baily, R. O., 1959
  - Baker, Adelaide N., undated
  - Baker, Robert, 1956
  - Baker (H. J.) & Bros., 1954
  - Baldwin, Hanson W., 1944-1967
  - Baldwin, Roger N., 1945-1961
  - Balkunas, Monsignor John, 1956-1973
  - Ball, George W., 1965-1973
  - Ball, Senator Joseph H., 1945
  - Ball, William B., 1951
  - Balog, Stephen James, 1957
  - Bamberger, Catherine, 1947
  - Bankhead, Representative William B., 1940
  - Barbour, Walworth, 1946
  - Barlow, Ernesta, 1945?
  - Barnes, LaVerne P., 1956
  - Barnett, Frank R., 1956-1973
  - Baron, Murray, 1956-1971
  - Barr, Joseph F., 1957-1959
  - Barr, Stringfellow, 1945
  - Barrett, Edward W., 1955-1965
  - Barry, Representative Robert R., 1961
  - Bartok, Laszlo, 1963
  - Barzel, Rainer, 1964-1973
  - Batchelor, C. D., undated
  - Bator, Victor, 1957-1961
  - Battin, Representative James F., 1963
  - Battle, George Gordon, 1938
  - Bauer, Carl, 1959
  - Baumgarten, Bernice, 1945
  - Bayh, Senator Birch, 1963-1971
  - Beall, Jack, 1949
  - Bean, M. W., 1958
  - Beard, Charles A., 1946
  - Beaufort, John D., 1946
  - Bechtle, Friedrich, 1970
  - Becker, Abram G., 1946-1954
  - Becker, Hellmut, 1970
  - Beer, Karl Willy, 1967
  - Beer, Max, 1958-1961
  - Beezley, P. C., 1960
  - Beichman, Arnold, 1946-1973
  - Beinart, Melvin, 1965
  - Belaunde, Ambassador Victor A., 1959
  - Bel Geddes, Norman, 1949
  - Bell, Daniel, 1956
  - Bell, Elliott V., 1945-1956
  - Bell, Ulric, 1946
  - Bellmon, Senator Henry, 1969
  - Belosselsky, Serge, 1946
  - Belous, Charles, 1949
  - Bender, Senator George H., 1956
  - Bennett, F. M., 1954
  - Bennett, John C., 1946
  - Bennett, T. Francis, 1947-1948
  - Bennett, Senator Wallace F., 1959
  - Bentley, Representative Alvin M., 1957-1959
  - Benton, Senator William, 1956
  - Berg, Mrs. Ragner, 1945
  - Bergel, Kurt, 1949
  - Berger, Mrs. William V., 1947
  - Bergerman, Milton M., 1940
  - Bergford, James W., 1970
  - Bergstraesser, Arnold, 1952-1961 (Box 63)
  - Berkowitz, J. H., 1939
  - Berkson, Seymour, 1948-1958
  - Berle, Adolf A., Jr., 1946-1969
  - Berle, Beatrice (Mrs. Adolf A., Jr.), 1971
  - Berman, Monty, 1940
  - Bernard, Ambassador Armand, 1959
  - Bernays, Edward L., 1954-1956
  - Bernstein, Henri, 1943-1945
  - Bertelotte, Cal, 1958
  - Bertke, Monsignor Stanley, 1948
  - Bertolette, C. M., 1956
  - Bethel, Paul D., 1965
  - Bevin, Ernest, 1947
  - Bidwell, Percy W., 1949
  - Biemiller, Andrew J., 1970
  - Bigelow, Gwladys W., 1940
  - Bingham, Alfred, 1947
  - Bingham, Representative Jonathan B., 1966
  - Binsse, Henry Lorin, 1946
  - Birdwood, Lord, 1959
  - Birkhead, Leon M., 1942-1946
  - Birrenbach, Kurt, 1963-1970
  - Bisgyer, Maurice, 1939-1940
  - Bishop, Kathleen, 1946
  - Bishop, Dr. Louis Faugeres, 1971
  - Bittner, Waclaw, 1945
  - Black, John H., 1973
  - Blackburn, Raymond, 1947
  - Blair, Ann, 1966
  - Blair, Edith, 1953
  - Blair, W. D., Jr., 1967
  - Blair, William, 1958
  - Blake, Peter, 1949
  - Blanchard, L., 1964
  - Blatnik, Representative John A., 1956
  - Blaustein, Jacob, 1940
  - Bliven, Bruce, 1947
  - Blomberg, Baron Frary von, 1969
  - Blood, Virginia, 1946-1947
  - Bloomingdale's, 1946
  - Blum, Evelyn, 1956
  - Blum, Robert, 1963-1964
  - Blume, Alvin L., 1940
  - Blumenfeld, Mr., 1939
  - Blumenfeld, Erik, 1950-1972
  - Blumgart, John D., 1958
  - Boardman, Harry, 1965-1967
  - Boas, Franz, 1939
  - Bodley, R. V. C., 1946
  - Boeker, Ambassador Alexander, 1946-1970
  - Boggs, Representative Hale, 1959-1968 (Box 64)
  - Bohm, Walter, 1964
  - Boland, Ambassador Frederick N., 1958
  - Boldyreff, C. W., 1956
  - Boll, Erwin, 1966
  - Bolling, Landrum, 1953
  - Bolte, Charles G., 1946
  - Bolton, Representative Frances P., 1948-1967
  - Bond, R. T., 1945
  - Bond, Ward, 1959
  - Bonesteel, Brigadier General C. H., III, 1955
  - Bonnard, Andre A., 1961
  - Bonnell, Maud H., 1973
  - Bonynge, Clarence, 1946
  - Boothby, Mr., 1945
  - Borchard, Edwin, 1946
  - Borchardt, Robert, 1958-1959
  - Borochowiez, Elly, 1964
  - Borries, Hans Karl von, 1951-1970
  - Borsig, Tet, 1950
  - Borsody, Stephen, 1946
  - Bosch, Representative Albert H., 1957
  - Boswell, William, 1960
  - Bosworth, William, 1973
  - Botelho, Viscount do, 1957
  - Boudreau, Frank G., 1941
  - Bourne, Russell, 1956-1967
  - Bow, Representative Frank T., 1969
  - Bowie, Robert R., 1963-1971
  - Bowie, W. Russell, 1940
  - Bowles, Representative Chester, 1947-1960
  - Bozell, L. Brent, 1959-1960
  - Brademas, Representative John, 1963-1973
  - Bradford, Robert F., 1945
  - Bradley, Harry, 1958
  - Brady, Annie, 1946
  - Brady, Colonel David, 1960
  - Brahinsky, Moses, 1965
  - Brandon, Donald W., 1963-1967
  - Brandon, Dorothy, 1952
  - Brandon, Henry, 1958
  - Brandt, Karl, 1948-1966
  - Brandt, Mrs. Karl, 1952
  - Brandt, Mayor Willy, 1963
  - Brasco, Representative Frank J., 1969
  - Brashich, Ranko M., 1970-1971
  - Brauer, Mayor Max, 1952
  - Braun, Ambassador Sigismund von, 1967
  - Braun, Theodore W., 1969
  - Breckinridge, Henry, 1941
  - Brennan, Donald G., 1972
  - Brenner, Anne Reed, 1939-1940
  - Berntano, Heinrich von, 1959-1963
  - Brettauer, A. E., 1946
  - Brettauer, Erwin Otto, 1946-1947
  - Brewer, Basil, 1956-1959
  - Brewer, (H. K.) & Co., 1946
  - Bridges, Senator Styles, 1945-1960
  - Briefs, Goetz, 1953
  - Brinckmann, R., 1970
  - Brinkley, J. W., 1961-1963
  - Brinton, Crane, 1949
  - Britt, George, 1961
  - Brock, Ray, 1946
  - Brod, Ernest, 1967
  - Bromley, Dorothy Dunbar, 1946-1955
  - Bromley, Keith, 1941
  - Brooke, Senator Edward W., 1969-1971
  - Brooks, Theodore, 1956
  - Brooks, Winslow, 1939
  - Bross, John A., 1963
  - Broughton, Mr., 1939 (Box 65)
  - Brown, Mr., 1956
  - Brown, Reverend Arthur Judson, 1939
  - Brown, Cecil, 1958
  - Brown, Constantine, 1955
  - Brown, H. W., 1947
  - Brown, Henry F., 1947
  - Brown, Irving, 1960-1966
  - Brown, Ralph A., 1968-1973
  - Brown, S. S., 1956
  - Bruessau, Werner, 1972
  - Brun, Captain Marcel J., 1946-1950
  - Brunini, John Gilland, 1967
  - Bryant, Anna, 1939
  - Bryant, Irene, 1970
  - Bryant, S. W., Jr., 1946
  - Bryson, Lyman, 1945-1949
  - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, 1963-1972
  - Bucerius, Gerd, 1950-1960
  - Buchanan, Representative John H., Jr., 1967
  - Buck, Mrs. J. L. Blair, 1947
  - Buck, Pearl S., 1945-1946
  - Buckley, Daniel G., 1959
  - Buckley, Priscilla L., 1960-1973
  - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1952-1973
  - Buckley, William F., Sr., 1954-1955
  - Budenz, Louis, 1951
  - Budreckis, Algirdas M., 1965-1968
  - Buell, Raymond Leslie, 1941-1945
  - Bulgarian National Council, 1960
  - Bullis, Harry A., 1958
  - Bullock, Hugh, 1954
  - Bundy, McGeorge, 1966
  - Bundy, William P., 1967-1974
  - Burghard, George, 1935
  - Burke, Eldon R., 1949
  - Burke, John S., 1941
  - Burlingham, Charles C., 1940-1946
  - Burnham, James, 1954-1972
  - Burnham, Marcia (Mrs. James), 1957
  - Burnham, Philip, 1946-1947
  - Burrowes, Arthur V., 1958
  - Bursten, Martin A., 1958
  - Bush, Senator Prescott, 1956
  - Bussche, Axel von dem, 1958
  - Butler, Senator John Marshall, 1959
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray, 1946-1947
  - Butterfield, Victor L., 1949
  - Buttinger, Joseph, 1955-1966
  - Byrd, Senator Harry F., Jr., 1967-1969
  - Byrd, Senator Robert C., 1957-1969
  - Byrne, James MacGregor, 1938-1973
  - Byrnes, James F., 1946 (Box 66)
  - Byroade, Ambassador Henry A., 1950-1956
  - CARE, 1947
  - CBS-TV, 1963
  - Cage, Penelope B., 1963
  - Cahn, Alexander, 1945
  - Cahnman, Werner J., 1953-1954
  - Calcagno, Peter J., 1963
  - Calderon, Joseph, 1947-1950
  - Caldwell, Robert J., 1946
  - California Intelligence Bureau, 1957
  - Calmer, Ned, 1965
  - Camaret, Michel de, 1957
  - Campbell, Charles E., Jr., 1953-1966
  - Campbell, John C., 1963-1972
  - Campion, Father Donald R., 1970-1973
  - Canaan, Gershon, 1968-1973
  - Canby, Henry S., 1958
  - Canfield, Cass, 1947-1965
  - Canham, Irwin, 1945-1956
  - Cannon, Senator Howard W., 1959-1972
  - Cannon, May Marshall, 1965
  - Capehart, Senator Homer E., 1959-1960
  - Carey, James B., 1961
  - Carey, Father Philip A., 1945
  - Cargo, Governor David F., 1969
  - Carman, Harry, 1949
  - Carmen, William, 1957
  - Carmichael, Joel, 1957-1970
  - Carroll, Monsignor Howard J., 1948-1950
  - Carstens, Karl, 1964
  - Carter, Edward C., 1943
  - Carter, Virginia, 1946
  - Carville, Mme. de, 1945
  - Case, Senator Clifford P., 1956-1971
  - Casey, John L., Jr., 1961-1962
  - Casey, William J., 1960-1969
  - Caspari, Fritz, 1967
  - Cassani, Henry R., 1957
  - Catholic News, 1945
  - Catton, Bruce, 1940-1941
  - Cavert, Samuel McCrea, undated
  - Celler, Representative Emanuel, 1960-1961
  - Centro Brasileiro da Europa Livre, 1958
  - Chace, James, 1972
  - Chadbourne, William M., 1946-1953
  - Chaffee, Stewart W., 1948-1950
  - Chamberlain, John R., 1945-1971
  - Chamberlain, William Henry, 1947-1952
  - Chambers, Julia Lytle, 1940
  - Chandler, Porter R., 1961
  - Chanler, William C., 1946
  - Chaplin, W. W., 1947
  - Chapman, Alvah H., Jr., 1958
  - Chapman, Emmanuel, 1940
  - Charles-Roux, Francois, 1944
  - Chase, Borden, 1959
  - Chase, Harriet, 1944
  - Chase, Ilka, 1941
  - Chellas, Allen, 1955
  - Chen, Chih Mai, 1948-1952
  - Cherne, Leo, 1945-1973
  - Chicago Round Table Forum, 1946 (Box 67)
  - Childs, John L., 1944-1946
  - Childs, Marquis, 1949
  - Childs, Richard S., 1946
  - Choate, Joseph H., Jr., 1946
  - Choo, Ida M., 1946
  - Chorin, Francis, 1960
  - Chow, Fabian, 1945
  - Christensen, Inga Hoegsbro, 1947-1959
  - Christian Educational Association, 1960
  - Christopher, Louis, 1946
  - Christopher, Robert, 1972
  - Christov, Luben M., 1956-1963
  - Chuong, Ambassador Tran Van, 1956
  - Chuong, Mme. Tran Van, 1961
  - Church, Edgar M., 1956
  - Church, Senator Frank, 1959
  - Church, Representative Ralph E., 1947
  - Ciechanowski, Jan, 1947
  - Ciolkosz, Adam, 1959
  - Clare Immaculate, Sister, 1966
  - Clark, Charles Upson, 1946
  - Clark, Evans, 1946
  - Clark, Grenville, 1944
  - Clark, Senator Joseph S., 1959
  - Clark, General Mark W., 1958
  - Clark, Rhoda, 1945-1946
  - Clark, Richard, 1964
  - Clark, Stephen C., 1941
  - Clark, Tom, undated
  - Clark, William, 1954
  - Clary, Count Marcus, 1973
  - Clay, General Lucius D., 1958-1973
  - Clayman, Jacob, 1970
  - Clering, Elizabeth, 1940
  - Cleveland, Ambassador Harlan, 1963-1968
  - Cleveland, Harold van B., 1968-1972
  - Clifford, Kathleen, 1946
  - Clinchy, Reverend Everett J., 1944
  - Clise, James William, 1959
  - Cobb, Henry Ives, Jr., 1962
  - Coblentz, Gaston, 1948-1971
  - Cohelan, Representative Jeffery, 1959-1968
  - Cohen, Arthur A., 1962
  - Cohen, Elliot E., 1949-1953
  - Cole, Felix, 1956
  - Collier, David S., 1962-1968
  - Comanduras, Dr. Peter, 1958
  - Combs, George Hamilton, 1945-1969
  - Como, Perry, 1964
  - Conant, James Bryant, 1947-1972
  - Confederacion Interamericana de Defensa del Continente, 1957
  - Conklin, Gilbert, 1959
  - Connelly, Matthew, 1948
  - Conning, Brace, 1962
  - Considine, Bob, 1957-1966
  - Conte, Representative Silvio O., 1964
  - Conway, Father Edward A., 1946-1949
  - Cook, F. G. Alletson, 1947
  - Cooke, Dwight, 1949
  - Coolidge, Archibald C., 1953
  - Cooper, Senator John Sherman, 1959-1973
  - Cooper, Merian C., 1967
  - Copland, Aaron, 1949
  - Corbett, Sarah Anne, 1948
  - Corsi, Edward, 1947
  - Coser, Lewis A., undated
  - Coste, Brutus, 1953-1973
  - Costin, Glen G., 1954 (Box 68)
  - Cotton, Senator Norris, 1963
  - Coudert, Representative Frederic R., Jr., 1956
  - Coughlin, Representative Lawrence, 1969
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1945-1947
  - Counterattack, 1958
  - Counts, George Sylvester, 1945-1961
  - Cousins, Norman, 1949-1973
  - Cowles, W. H., 1958
  - Cox, Arthur, 1952
  - Crabbs, Robert O., 1959
  - Cramer, Ernst J., 1970-1971
  - Crane, Joan, 1950
  - Crane, Josephine, 1945-1953
  - Crawford, Boyd, 1947
  - Crawford, George G., undated
  - Crawford, Kenneth G., 1968
  - Creel, George, 1945-1947
  - Crittenberger, Lieutenant General Willis D., 1957-1958
  - Croan, Melvin, 1971-1973
  - Crofts, Elizabeth, 1955
  - Cronin, Father John F., 1946-1964
  - Cronkite, Walter, 1958
  - Crook, Dorothy, 1958-1961
  - Crosby, Robert R., Jr., 1941
  - Cross, S. H., 1941
  - Crowe, Gwen, 1957
  - Cruikshank, Robin, 1947
  - Culhane, Father Eugene K., 1964-1968
  - Cummings, E. E., 1949
  - Cuneo, Ernest, 1947
  - Currier, Raymond P., 1952
  - Curry, Alma M., 1941
  - Curtis, Senator Carl, 1969
  - Curtius, Klaus, 1964-1969
  - Cushing, Richard Cardinal, 1960-1961
  - Cutting, C. Suydam, 1959
  - Czaja, Dr., 1970
  - Czarnecki, Anthony, 1945
  - Czechlewski, Joseph, 1946
  - Czyz, Jaroslav, 1949
  - Daily Express (London), 1947
  - Daily Telegraph amd Morning Post (London), 1947
  - Dalma, Alfons, 1965-1966
  - Daly, John, 1958
  - Damrosch, Walter, 1944
  - Danielopol, Dimitri, 1965
  - Dargas, Antoni, 1959
  - Darien, Sid, 1953
  - Darkow, Marguerite D., 1939
  - Davenport, Marcia, 1946
  - Davenport, Russell, 1941-1951
  - Davidson, Ben, 1964-1965
  - Davie, May, 1946-1957
  - Davies, Gordon, 1973
  - Davila, Carlos, 1946
  - Davis, Elmer, 1946-1952
  - Davis, John W., 1944-1946
  - Davis, Richard, 1962
  - Davis, Robert Gorham, 1949
  - Davis, Sammy, Jr., 1964
  - Davis, Father Thurston N., 1956-1969 (Box 69)
  - Dawson, Mrs., 1945
  - Dawson, Albert K., 1947
  - Dawson, Archie O., 1948
  - Day, Edmund E., 1947-1949
  - Day, John, 1958
  - Deadline Data on World Affairs, 1960-1961